[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
The girl from Roopkund is alive.
Kyoichi Nanase claimed she was dead.
Shiharu is dead.
But I don't believe him.
You won't look into anything unnecessary?
If anything, he seems desperate to hide her.
I want nothing to do with this.
Please, wait. Shii...
The girl from Roopkund needs you!
She was already weak the last time I saw her.
You're the only person who can save her!
Shiharu was an artificially made human being.
Haruka.
- What are you doing? - Don't you love me?
You're acting strange.
What do you love about me?
Huh?
Answer me.
I love everything about you.
And what's "everything"?
Your pretty hair, your beauty, your intelligence - everything.
Then you wouldn't love me if I became bald, ugly, and dumb.
Well, that wouldn't be you anymore, would it?
Yeah.
I think so, too.
Shiharu?
Wait.
Shiharu.
Shiharu!
If something's bothering you, tell me.
I already did!
I don't understand.
That's fine.
Don't make things more confusing for me.
I don't want you to understand.
Does that clear things up?
Fine.
[The mystery of his sister's life and death] [Despair hidden within the truth]
I'm home.
[log.7]
Shiharu?
Aren't you home?
So it's been quite some time since she's lost her ability to walk.
Could you tell me more about the marks on her skin?
The ones I saw were on her hands and neck.
I see.
The clone's DNA suffered damages after all.
But if you're telling the truth,
then it's entirely possible she's still alive.
Though I suspect she doesn't have long.
Nanase and Ishimizaki did well to keep her thriving without me.
Dr. Senba.
Please ask Mr. Nanase where he's keeping her.
- Me? - I know he would tell you.
Because you can save her.
He would never pass up such an opportunity.
My answer is "no".
I can't afford to get involved anymore.
You aren't worried about her?
I am interested. But that's all.
You brought her into this world.
Your trivial moral reasoning won't change my mind.
So you don't think of her as your daughter?
My "daughter".
A child I knew nothing about for 30 years, my "daughter".
They ought to realize their selfish desires
ruined any potential for scientific advancements.
Nanase is especially guilty in that regard.
- I just... - Quiet.
Their actions have brought very real consequences to my life.
I just want her be alive.
I called my security on you.
Feel free to stay if you want to be arrested.
I can't be entertaining this any longer.
What are you doing here?
Sir.
Isn't there something you've been hiding from me?
What are you referring to?
As I was looking into our finances,
I noticed some funds related to "log.0" were still being utilized.
They were deftly hidden through distributions to a shell corporation.
Sir, did you think I wouldn't notice?
You taught me to be thorough.
What is the money being used for?
Order me to keep it under wraps, and I will.
But must I be kept in the dark as well?
Please, tell me the truth.
Is "log.0" still active?
I wouldn't know.
Morning. Did you get it?
Yes. Everything pertaining to Roopkund.
Score.
Want a drink to celebrate?
Maybe it's too early for that.
Take a seat wherever.
I run this bar.
Just kidding.
I rented the place so we'd get some privacy.
Honestly, I drank till morning 'cause I didn't want to go home.
Was too scared to find myself alone and all.
Some crazy truth we got ourselves, huh?
Do you believe them? It sounds ridiculous to me.
I'm more convinced, knowing Kayoko Senba is involved.
Excuse me.
- Sir. - Yes?
You won't release our names, right?
No, of course not. I promise.
I only ask because of the rumors. Not like I believe them, but...
Rumors?
They say those who bring trouble to Plantae
are punished by the spirit of the Holy One.
I assume my fellow journalist, Onodera,
was murdered by this "spirit" of theirs.
All that's left is his bones, and nothing else.
That man, Ushio.
Is he acting on Plantae's orders?
Who else would boss him around?
Kyoichi Nanase.
Their interests do align.
But I'm more inclined to believe this is all Plantae.
The biggest surprise here,
is that they went and created a person.
No country in the world would legalize human clones.
But the technology in creating one holds great value.
Medical advancements would surge forth.
Find evidence of this clone at once.
We'll contact the main branch in China afterwards.
Yes, sir.
I've checked its contents.
Everything pertains to the making of a clone.
So it's all true.
There really was an artificial human
walking among us.
Sends shivers down my spine, I tell you.
I bet Onodera felt the same way.
We can't help it.
It's what makes us journalists.
I'll be sure his findings see a proper conclusion.
I don't want you to write about this.
My sister's existence will be known to the world.
Don't worry.
I won't be hasty about publishing our evidence.
I'll hold onto the data.
It'll be useful as a bargaining chip to find my sister.
I promise not to put you in a bind.
Publishing an article will do that anyway.
Numerous people have died over this.
Leave it be, and more will follow.
You plan to publish the article immediately.
These people are killing folks left and right
all to keep this girl under wraps.
The public deserves to know.
Then what happens to my sister?
"Punished by the spirit of the Holy One".
Hear what I'm getting at?
What do you mean?
The "Holy One" they're so scared of,
is your sister, the Holy Woman.
What sort of assumption is that?
I won't beat around the bush.
I suspect your younger sister is the one behind all this.
What?
Why Shiharu?
She wants to protect herself.
Your sister is the Holy Woman.
If anyone could control Ushio, it'd be her.
And your father.
He was all in on helping Plantae
create a clone.
It wouldn't surprise me if he obeys the Holy Woman, too.
- Give me that! - Hey!
Think about it!
Shiharu Nanase is an artificial human being!
Can you really call a thing like her your sister?
Let go!
[Yui Ishimizaki]
[Kyoichi told me everything about Shiharu]
[Senba]
Damn it, why isn't anyone answering?
Tomoe is a stay-at-home mother. I assumed she would be around.
Guess we'll wait.
We can't stay long. We're ignoring orders to be here.
Still a bootlicker for headquarters?
Tada.
Damn it!
I thought you'd feel more comfortable meeting where there's a crowd.
- Want a croquette? - What did he tell you about Shiharu?
Everything.
Roopkund, the process... Everything.
Where is Shiharu?
Kyoichi said she had passed away.
- But I think she's alive! - Who are you?
Answer me.
I'm Ishimizaki's daughter, Mari.
What?
I met Mari. She was in a wheelchair.
The Professor called that girl his daughter.
My father lied to you.
He had no choice.
Why?
Why did he have to lie?
Who were you looking for all this time?
The Professor brought that girl in, on the day of a heavy storm?
Right.
But you can't tell me who this girl is.
Why?
Because I promised her I wouldn't.
What's the point of a promise like that?
I'm not hiding anything else from you.
I know I'm asking the impossible, but I want you to trust me.
Haruka, I promise you and I share a goal.
Alright.
I'm sorry about your father. That must have been difficult.
He was one of the few individuals who truly understood me.
He'd always entertain my thoughts, too.
I could tell him anything.
But in these last few years, he changed.
The last time I saw him
was another day I couldn't ask about his secrets.
Didn't notice you there.
How's Shii?
She's sleeping right now.
Let her rest.
Shiharu is okay.
I promise.
Okay.
Dad. Have you been eating?
Huh?
Oh, yes. I have.
Let me whip up something for you.
What?
Mari...
I don't need to worry about you anymore.
Everyone will come to love your endearing attitude.
Stop it, you're embarrassing me.
Never change, Mari.
I won't.
My father was prepared to confess about Roopkund.
I regret not asking.
I should have pestered him more.
Maybe something would have changed.
That regret is why I'm so determined now.
It'll be okay, Haruka.
We will find Shiharu. I promise.
What if...
What if we find Shiharu, and she's changed?
What do you mean?
Someone suspects Shiharu is the one behind all these incidents.
That's impossible.
It's really not.
Anyone who suspects her is a fool.
Yeah.
They're a fool.
I don't understand.
Like I said, I didn't get the evidence.
I'll try again from another angle.
Kayoko Senba seems like my best bet.
What happened to Haruka Nanase?
He gave me nothing to work with.
I'll change his mind.
Tell me how to reach him.
That's not my information to give.
- I know it's written in there. - Hey, no touching.
This is a journalist's soul.
Kayoko Senba, you said?
That's right. Let's forget Haruka Nanase.
I'm so sorry.
I only have instant foods.
But you should definitely eat something.
I'll heat up the croquettes.
Right, I should boil the water first.
Here, I'll do it.
Thank you.
Haruka.
Could you tell me more about Shiharu?
Huh?
You told me stories about her before.
Please?
She once said she wanted a part-time job.
What I considered a pain, was a source of wonder to her.
What're you doing?
Welcome home.
I just finished reading.
Then let's go to the gallery.
Haruka, you don't work part-time?
No, why?
It seems fun.
"Manager, that's not what the manual says."
Huh? What manager?
I just wanted to try saying it.
"That's not my mistake."
"I meant to come in, really."
Is that for when you skip work?
I don't know.
I wouldn't know.
Work is more trouble than it's worth.
Then how's this? "Hasegawa, we share a shift on Christmas."
Who the heck is Hasegawa?
"No venting allowed, Haruka."
I'm employed with you?
I usually started our conversations.
Shiharu would be too absorbed in a book.
Thank you.
For telling me about her.
It's no use.
I could contact Kayoko Senba's son,
but he said his mother left for a vacation.
I see.
What're you up to?
I figured I'd stop being a corporate bootlicker.
The police contacted you?
No. Don't tell a soul I'm here.
I'll be fine.
You take care as well, alright?
Sir, the elevator is for guests only.
May I ask for your room key?
Has Tomoe contacted you?
What is that woman doing?
I hope you've been feeding Keita well.
Room service is here.
I'll stay in touch.
I've brought your water.
Would you leave it inside?
Of course.
[Mikio Maehara]
[Tsuyoshi Kojima] [Xin Ming Ah Japan Representative]
[Dear Haruka Nanase, I believe we can assist you...]
Haruka! Where are you going?
To meet someone. I'll be fine alone.
Wait.
"Do all that you can today, to see further progress tomorrow."
I know that one. Isaac Newton.
Not bad.
You really came alone.
I wouldn't disobey the President's son.
Without telling my father?
What did you need to ask me?
Or is this about your father?
Tell me where Shiharu is.
Her again.
I have the all the findings from Roopkund.
What are you referring to?
The research you people are so desperate to hide.
Show me, and maybe it'll ring a bell.
Creating Shiharu from the bones of Roopkund. Does that help?
Please.
Tell me where she is.
Where is Shiharu?
Create?
You say we "created" your sister?
Drop the act, now.
That girl only exists in your mind.
Are you like Kayoko Senba?
Were you also told the cloning was a failure?
No, I won't believe that.
Because you people...
You people murdered Professor Ishimizaki to keep Shiharu a secret!
- What? - And he's not the only one you've killed!
I see.
I get it now.
Your search has brought plenty of others misfortune.
Kyoichi Nanase's the one giving orders.
He just wants to keep his company afloat!
I can't be entertaining your delusions.
You're his right-hand man. I know you know everything!
What?
I don't know anything.
Not a damn thing.
Mari.
Is this about...
I'm sorry. We haven't made much progress in regards to your father's case.
I see.
But this case is strange, in many ways.
So I had something I wanted to ask.
Alright.
When Nanase was attacked by the man named Ushio,
he claimed he was accompanied by Professor Ishimizaki's niece.
But that was you, wasn't it?
Well, I...
I'm not trying to interrogate you about that.
Let me rephrase my question.
You were helping Nanase search for his sister, correct?
Except, this sister of his doesn't exist on paper.
I want to start by searching for this person.
What?
This time, I want to try believing in Haruka Nanase.
Is there anything you know about Shiharu Nanase?
People who have no citizenship each have their own reasons.
If Shiharu is in a similar situation, we must find her right away.
As it stands now,
she's unable to receive legal medical attention should she need it.
Shiharu Nanase exists somewhere, doesn't she?
Reach out again when you're ready to talk.
I mostly wanted to break the ice today.
Haruka. Where are you?
Is Shiharu dead?
You must've heard from Ishimizaki's daughter.
How can you act so nonchalant?
You...
Do you realize what you've done?
Of course.
Did you...
Did you kill Shiharu?
You used my mother to create a clone.
Isn't that why she died?
Who told you that?
Kayoko Senba.
I have all the files on Roopkund as well.
What sort of stunts did you pull?
I haven't caused anyone trouble.
At least, not yet.
Haruka.
Shiharu is alive.
Shiharu is very much alive.
You must realize the information you have is a burden to her.
Why?
Why are you doing all this?
Everything I do is for Shiharu's sake.
Where is she?
Where the hell is Shiharu?
Let's talk in person. Alone.
Trust me.
You have no other choice.
"No venting allowed, Haruka."
I'm glad you've come.
Follow me.
You've made a sound decision, Haruka Nanase.
You said you'd help, but how?
Please, have a seat.
I hear you suspect your step-father and head of Nichie Pharmaceutical,
Kyoichi Nanase, of a number of things.
What bothers you most? The thing with your mother?
Or your missing sister?
I see Hirama has told you of my situation.
I will admit. We have done our own investigating as well.
As such, I believe our goals are aligned with one another.
How so?
If Nichie goes under, it becomes easier for both of us to take action.
Nichie Pharmaceutical - or rather, Kyoichi Nanase,
who has dabbled in cloning tech, is now Plantae's loyal dog.
Let me cut to the chase.
Please think of this money as our way of aiding your search.
What is it you want from me?
You have the data on Roopkund, yes?
I had a feeling.
Our hope is for Nichie to be officially prosecuted.
Furthermore,
we plan to re-establish the company as a trustworthy corporation.
Though human cloning is illegal,
the technology behind it can be used for medical advancements.
I was a fool for expecting anything from you.
Negotiations haven't ended yet.
Think about it.
The circumstances surrounding Shiharu grow unruly by the day.
Surely, you cannot protect her alone.
I suspect your younger sister is the one behind all this.
We will hold onto the data, for your own safety as well.
A wise choice indeed.
Don't ever bother me again.
You're in my way.
Bastard...
If I don't report back to Hirama, he will call the police on you.
It seems there's been a misunderstanding.
I only wished to talk business with you.
Well, I'm not interested.
Then please, make your way out.
You alright?
Barely.
So? Did you get anything good out of them?
No.
Figures.
Sorry about my accusations yesterday.
So, what's your next move?
The same as it's always been.
Find my sister.
Shii, could you give this a taste?
Sure.
That tastes wrong.
It's good enough.
It's not.
"Do all that you can today, to see further progress tomorrow."
I know that one.
- Isaac Newton! - Isaac Newton!
Hello?
Please help me find Shiharu Nanase.
A package, for me?
[Keita]